animesh bista

Academic Counselor

As an organised and highly creative individual i love the challenges of working with in dynamic and faster paced working environment. The knowledge gained from my corporate experience with the companies such as My Foods worldwide and Kangaroo Education Foundation has shaped my ability to adapt quickly, work efficiently, think creatively and work effectively as part of a team or own my



animeshbistanepal@gmail.com

+977 9823004111

Buddhashanti -03, Hellochowk, Budhabare, Nepal

WORK EXPERIENCE

Supervisor

My Foods Worldwide Pvt. Ltd

02/2011 - 04/2014 London

Afro foods production company, food packaging, label designing Achievements/Tasks

 Supervising, Training, Label designing, Documentation work

Contact: Mr. Abdulla Hassan - +44 7544 466666

Title/Position Kangaroo Education Foundation

05/2016 - Present Birtamode, Nepal Educational Consultant/Foreign Visa Lodgement, Language Training Achievements/Tasks

 Abroad Study Counselor, Interview preparation, Documentation & visa Lodgement

Contact: Nabin Dhungana – nabin@kangaroo.edu.np

EDUCATION

BTEC Level-7 Extended Diploma Greenwich London College

09/2013 - 09/2014

London, United Kingdom

Courses

 Strategic management Leadership Skills

- HRM
- Organisation Behavior
- Project management

Diploma

Greenwich London College

10/2011 - 06/2013 London, United Kingdom

Courses

HRM

Accountancy

HRD

Organisation Behavior

Certificate in TTHM West end London College

10/2009 - 06/2011 London, United Kingdom

SKILLS

Prioritizing **Public Speaking Goal Setting Fitness Problem Solving** Self-Discipline **Finances** Decision making Genuiness Critical and thinking

ACHIEVEMENTS

Graduation Honored (06/2014)

Graduation Ceremony by Education Provider in UK

CERTIFICATES

Aim Track Institute (03/2008 – 09/2008) Computer Operator Course

Dahal Driving School (01/2016 – 04/2016) Car Driving Lesson

ORGANIZATIONS

Green-wish Fitness Club (04/2016 – Present) Gym Instructor Physical

The Revolution Youth Club (02/2015 – Present) President

LANGUAGES

English Hindi Nepali

INTERESTS

Sports Learning Driving Travel Cooking

Teaching Gaming